Department of Drama and Dance Records UA070
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Drama Department Productions, 1878 -- 1993; UA070.001; 18.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 1 Artifact(s); 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Paul and Virginia, 1916; UA070.001.028.00019 (Box 28)
  - Roaches, 1970; UA070.001.028.00020 (Box 28)
  - The Stale Animal, 1940 -- 1944; UA070.001.028.00021 (Box 28)
  - To Giovanni and Guiseppe Socini, n.d., UA070.001.028.00022 (Box 28)
  - Voter's Choice, 1952; UA070.001.028.00023 (Box 28)
  - Worlds, 1940; UA070.001.028.00024 (Box 28)
  - Challenge, n.d., UA070.001.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - A Tufts Phantasy, n.d., UA070.001.029.00002 (Box 29)
  - Decision, n.d., UA070.001.029.00003 (Box 29)
  - Lessons to Dante, n.d., UA070.001.029.00004 (Box 29)
  - Medea, n.d., UA070.001.029.00005 (Box 29)
  - Nothin' and Nobody, n.d., UA070.001.029.00006 (Box 29)
  - One-Act Play, n.d., UA070.001.029.00007 (Box 29)
  - One-Act Play by Lois Epstein, n.d., UA070.001.029.00008 (Box 29)
  - One-Act Play by George Niles, n.d., UA070.001.029.00009 (Box 29)
  - The Forgotten Quantity, n.d., UA070.001.029.00010 (Box 29)
  - Top of the World, n.d., UA070.001.029.00011 (Box 29)
  - The Tranhope Ark, n.d., UA070.001.029.00012 (Box 29)
  - Drama Department: Press Clippings, 1907 -- 1974; UA070.001.030 (Box Shared 75)
  - Drama Department: Magic Circle Productions, 1952 -- 1964; UA070.001.031 (Box Shared 76)
  - Drama Department: Tufts Community Players -- production photographs, "The Rose Tattoo", 1954; UA070.001.032 (Box Shared 77)
  - Drama Department: Photos, Junior Class Play, "The Other Way", 1909; UA070.001.033 (Box Shared 78)
  - The Tufts Graduate Dramatic Society: A History, 1928 -- 1948; UA070.001.034.00001 (Box 34)
  - Drama Dept., The Medea Project, 1977; UA070.001.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Drama Dept., The Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1978; UA070.001.036.00002 (Box 36)
  - Drama Dept., All My Sons, 1979; UA070.001.036.00003 (Box 36)
  - Drama Dept., The Haunted House, 1979; UA070.001.036.00004 (Box 36)
  - Drama Dept., The Sea, 1979; UA070.001.036.00005 (Box 36)
  - Drama Dept., The Diary of Anne Frank, 1978; UA070.001.036.00006 (Box 36)
  - Drama Dept., Agamemnon, 1980; UA070.001.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Drama Dept., Camino Real, 1980; UA070.001.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Drama Dept., The Tempest, 1980; UA070.001.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Drama Dept., Ladyhouse Blues, 1981; UA070.001.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Drama Dept., The Miser, 1981; UA070.001.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Drama Dept., Royal Hunt of the Sun, 1981; UA070.001.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Drama Dept., Dead Souls, 1982; UA070.001.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Drama Dept., Waiting for Godot, 1982; UA070.001.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - Drama Dept., The Hostage, 1972; UA070.001.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., The Insect Comedy, 1972; UA070.001.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., MacBeth, 1972; UA070.001.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., The Cherry Orchard, 1973; UA070.001.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., Ghosts, 1975; UA070.001.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., Endgame, 1976; UA070.001.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., The Lady from the Sea, 1976; UA070.001.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Drama Dept., Threepenny Opera, 1977; UA070.001.039.00008 (Box 39)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, (Three) One Act Plays, 1938; UA070.001.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, Darkness and Dawn, 1948; UA070.001.040.00002 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, The Bedtime Story, 1952; UA070.001.040.00003 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, Goodnight Caroline, 1952; UA070.001.040.00004 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, Private Lives, 1955; UA070.001.040.00005 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, The Affairs of Anatol, 1958; UA070.001.040.00006 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, The Member of the Wedding, 1958; UA070.001.040.00007 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, Twilight Crane, 1958; UA070.001.040.00008 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, King Richard II, 1959; UA070.001.040.00009 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, Dame Judith Anderson, 1962; UA070.001.040.00010 (Box 40)
  - Dept. of Drama and Speech, Children of Darkness, 1963; UA070.001.040.00011 (Box 40)
  - Arena Theater, PR releases and clippings, 1966 -- 1969; UA070.001.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Arena Theater, publicity releases, 1970 -- 1972; UA070.001.053.00002 (Box 53)
  - Arena Theater, publicity releases, 1973 -- 1974; UA070.001.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - Arena Theater, dramatic productions, pr releases, 1975 -- 1978; UA070.001.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Arena Theater Chair Swatches, 1909; UA070.001.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Arena Theater Chair, 1909; UA070.001.053.00006 (Box Shared 8)
    The chair is upholstered in black and has a wooden base; it was removed from Arena Theater before it was demolished in 1991; it may be the original chair installed when the theater first opened 1909; there are swatches of upholstering from the Arena Theater chairs in UA070/001-041#00005
- Drama Department photographic slides of productions, 1959 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2000; UA070.003; 3.0 Linear Feet; 46 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains photographs of Drama Department productions.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Arena slides of Hank Azaria, UA070.003.041.00001 (Box 41)
    This box is undated.
  - Unidentified slides, UA070.003.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - The Electra/ Richard II, 1959; UA070.003.041.00003 (Box 41)
    Original box #: Box 1; Original description: Major
  - Exit the King, 1973; UA070.003.041.00004 (Box 41)
    Director: Harry M. Ritchie. Original box #: Box 2; Original description: Summer
  - What the Butler Saw, 1973; UA070.003.041.00005 (Box 41)
    Director: Lester W. Thompson, Jr. Original box #: Box 3; Original description: Summer
  - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1973; UA070.003.041.00006 (Box 41)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 4; Original description: Summer
  - A View from the Bridge, 1973; UA070.003.041.00007 (Box 41)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 5; Original description: Summer
  - Awake and Sing, 1973; UA070.003.041.00008 (Box 41)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 6; Original description: Major
  - Gloaming, O My Darling, 1974; UA070.003.041.00009 (Box 41)
    Director: Mitchell Englemeyer. Original box #: Box 8; Original description: Cand S
  - Private Lives, 1974; UA070.003.041.00010 (Box 41)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 9; Original description: Summer
  - Death of a Salesman, 1974; UA070.003.041.00011 (Box 41)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 10; Original description: Summer
  - Blithe Spirit, 1975; UA070.003.041.00012 (Box 41)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 11; Original description: Summer
  - Ryan's Yorktown Tune and Lobsterback, 1975; UA070.003.041.00013 (Box 41)
    Director (Ryan's Yorktown Tune): Harry M. Ritchie, (Lobsterback): Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 12; Original description: Summer
  - Lobsterback, 1975; UA070.003.041.00014 (Box 41)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 13; Original Description: Summer
  - Richard III, 1975; UA070.003.041.00015 (Box 41)
    Director: Lester Thompson. Original box #: Box 14; Original description: Major
  - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, 1976; UA070.003.041.00016 (Box 41)
    Director: Ernie Stewart. Original box #: Box 15; Original description: Summer
  - The Crucible, 1976; UA070.003.041.00017 (Box 41)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 16; Original description: Major
  - Luv, 1976; UA070.003.041.00018 (Box 41)
    Original box #: 17A; Original description: Summer
  - Calls out Billy Morgan, 1976; UA070.003.042.00001 (Box 42)
    Original box #: 18; Original description: Summer
  - Endgame, 1976; UA070.003.042.00002 (Box 42)
    Original box #: Box 19; Original description: Major
  - The Lady from the Sea, 1976; UA070.003.042.00003 (Box 42)
    Original description: Major
  - Dutchman, 1977; UA070.003.042.00004 (Box 42)
    Original box #: Box 21; Original description: Card S
  - The Morning After Optimism, 1977; UA070.003.042.00005 (Box 42)
    Original box #: Box 22; Original description: Masters
  - You Never Can Tell, 1977; UA070.003.042.00006 (Box 42)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: 23B; Original description: Summer
  - The Three Cuckolds, 1977; UA070.003.042.00007 (Box 42)
    Director: Eric Forsythe. Original box #: Box 24; Original description: Summer
  - The Congresswoman, 1977; UA070.003.042.00008 (Box 42)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 25; Original description: Major
  - The Tooth of Crime, 1977; UA070.003.042.00009 (Box 42)
    Director: Jan Kirschner. Original box #: Box 26; Original description: Major
  - The Love Suicides at Amijima, 1978; UA070.003.042.00010 (Box 42)
    Director: Eric Forsythe. Original box #: Box 27; Original description: Major
  - French Gray, 1978; UA070.003.042.00011 (Box 42)
    Director: Stephanie Marco-Puleo. Original box #: Box 28; Original description: Masters
  - She Stoops to Conquer, 1978; UA070.003.042.00012 (Box 42)
    Original description: Summer
  - She Stoops to Conquer, 1978; UA070.003.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - A Fable, 1978; UA070.003.042.00014 (Box 42)
    Director: Eric Forsythe. Original Description: Summer
  - A Fable, 1978; UA070.003.042.00015 (Box 42)
    Director: Eric Forsythe. Original description: Summer
  - Tobacco Road, 1978; UA070.003.042.00016 (Box 42)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 29A; Original description: Summer
  - Tobacco Road, 1978; UA070.003.042.00017 (Box 42)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 29B; Original description: Summer
  - R, 1978; UA070.003.042.00018 (Box 42)
    Director: Jan Kirshner. Original box #: Box 31B; Original description: Summer
  - R, 1978; UA070.003.043.00001 (Box 43)
    Director: Jan Kirschner. Original box #: 31A; Original description: Summer
  - The Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1978; UA070.003.043.00002 (Box 43)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: 32B; Original description: Major
  - The Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1978; UA070.003.043.00003 (Box 43)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: 32A; Original description: Major
  - The Diary of Anne Frank, 1978; UA070.003.043.00004 (Box 43)
    Director: Kalman A. Burnim. Original box #: Box 33; Original description: Major
  - Jest!, 1979; UA070.003.043.00005 (Box 43)
    Director: Jan Kirscher. Original box #: Box 34; Original description: Major
  - The Sea, 1979; UA070.003.043.00006 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 35C; Original description: Major
    - Oliver Platt and three male students in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00006.00018 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (far left) and three male students in conversation in a university production of The Sea.
      Plays; Actors; Students; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Department of Drama and Dance; Bond, Edward
  - The Sea, 1979; UA070.003.043.00007 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 35A; Original description: Major
    - Oliver Platt with male and female student in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00007.00003 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (back, right) and two students observe an unidentified object in a scene from a university production of The Sea.
    - Oliver Platt with male and two female students in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00007.00006 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (back, middle) and two students observe an unidentified object, while a third student is laying down in a scene from a university production of The Sea.
    - Closeup of Oliver Platt in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00007.00023 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. A closeup of Oliver Platt in a university production of The Sea.
  - The Sea, 1979; UA070.003.043.00008 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 35B; Original description: Major
    - Oliver Platt watches student holding a knife in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00008.00004 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (back, right) and a female student look on as a male student holds a knife in a university production of The Sea.
    - Oliver Platt and three male students in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00008.00005 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (back) and three students look at an unidentified object in a university production of The Sea.
    - Oliver Platt and three male students in conversation in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00008.00019 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (far left) and three students hold a conversation in a university production of The Sea.
    - Oliver Platt sits and listens in The Sea, 1979-04-01; UA070.003.043.00008.00025 (Box 43)
      Director: Sherwood Collins. Oliver Platt (seated, left) and two male students sit and listen to a fourth male student in a university production of The Sea.
  - The Man who Came to Dinner, 1979; UA070.003.043.00009 (Box 43)
    Director: Rob Wright. Original box #: Box 36B; Original description: Summer
  - The Man who Came to Dinner, 1979; UA070.003.043.00010 (Box 43)
    Director: Rob Wright. Original box #: Box 36C; Original description: Summer
  - The Man who Came to Dinner, 1979; UA070.003.043.00011 (Box 43)
    Director: Rob Wright. Original box #: Box 36A; Original description: Summer
  - Open Season, 1979; UA070.003.043.00012 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: 37B; Original description: Summer
  - Open Season, 1979; UA070.003.043.00013 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: 37A; Original description: Summer
  - The School for Scandal, 1979; UA070.003.043.00014 (Box 43)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: 38B; Original description: Summer
  - The School for Scandal, 1979; UA070.003.043.00015 (Box 43)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: 38A; Original description: Summer
  - The Haunted House, 1979; UA070.003.043.00016 (Box 43)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 39; Original description: Major
  - All My Sons, 1979; UA070.003.043.00017 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 40B; Original description: Major
  - All My Sons, 1979; UA070.003.043.00018 (Box 43)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 40A; Original description: Major
  - Major Barbara (extras), 1980; UA070.003.044.00001 (Box 44)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 41A; Original description: Major
  - Agamemnon, 1980; UA070.003.044.00002 (Box 44)
    Director: Julie Portman. Original box #: Box 42; Original description: Major
  - Lion in Winter, 1980; UA070.003.044.00003 (Box 44)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 43; Original description: Summer
  - Holiday, 1980; UA070.003.044.00004 (Box 44)
    Director: Robert Wright. Original box #: Box 44B; Original description: Summer
  - Holiday, 1980; UA070.003.044.00005 (Box 44)
    Director: Robert Wright. Original box #: Box 44C; Original description: Summer
  - Holiday, 1980; UA070.003.044.00006 (Box 44)
    Director: Robert Wright. Original box #: Box 44A; Original description: Summer
  - Hay Fever, 1980; UA070.003.044.00007 (Box 44)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 45; Original description: Summer
  - The Imaginary Invalid, 1980; UA070.003.044.00008 (Box 44)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 46A; Original description: Summer
  - The Imaginary Invalid, 1980; UA070.003.044.00009 (Box 44)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 46B; Original description: Summer
  - Camino Real, 1980; UA070.003.044.00010 (Box 44)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 47C; Original description: Major
    - Oliver Platt in Camino Real, 1980-10-01; UA070.003.044.00010.00001; Unknown (Box 44)
      Director: Downing Cless. Oliver Platt is top right, the character in a panama and white suit.
      Plays; Students; Actors; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Williams, Tennessee, 1911-1983; Dept. of Drama and Dance
  - Camino Real, 1980; UA070.003.044.00011 (Box 44)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 47A; Original description: Major
  - Camino Real, 1980; UA070.003.044.00012 (Box 44)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 47B; Original description: Major
  - Big and Little, 1980; UA070.003.044.00013 (Box 44)
    Director: Daina Robins. Original box #: Box 48; Original description: Masters
  - The Tempest, 1980; UA070.003.044.00014 (Box 44)
    Director: Julie Portman. Original box #: Box 49A; Original description: Major
  - The Tempest, 1980; UA070.003.044.00015 (Box 44)
    Director: Julie Portman. Original box #: Box 49B; Original description: Major
  - Summit Conference, 1981; UA070.003.044.00016 (Box 44)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 50; Original description: Major
  - The Royal Hunt of the Sun, 1981; UA070.003.044.00017 (Box 44)
    Director: Kalman A. Burnim. Original box #: Box 51B; Original description: Major
  - The Royal Hunt of the Sun, 1981; UA070.003.044.00018 (Box 44)
    Director: Kalman A. Burnim. Original box #: Box 51A; Original description: Major
    - Oliver Platt stands in The Royal Hunt of the Sun, 1981-05-01; UA070.003.044.00018.00031 (Box 43)
      Director: Kalman A. Burnim. Oliver Platt (middle, front) stands guard in a university production of The Royal Hunt of the Sun.
      Plays; Actors; Students; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Department of Drama and Dance; Shaffer, Peter, 1926-
  - The Miser, 1981; UA070.003.045.00001 (Box 45)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 52; Original description: Major
    - Cast of The Miser, 1981-10-01; UA070.003.045.00001.00025 (Box 45)
      Theater; Drama; Students; Plays; photographic print; Moliere, 1622-1673
  - Lady House Blues, 1981; UA070.003.045.00002 (Box 45)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 53B; Original description: Major
  - Lady House Blues, 1981; UA070.003.045.00003 (Box 45)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 53A; Original description: Major
  - Waiting For Godot, 1982; UA070.003.045.00004 (Box 45)
    Director: Julie Portman. Original box #: Box 54; Original description: Major
    - Pozzo (played by Oliver Platt) and Lucky in Waiting for Godot, 1982-03-01; UA070.003.045.00004.00001; Unknown (Box 45)
      Director: Julie Portman.
      Actors; Plays; Students; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Beckett, Samuel, 1906-1989; Dept. of Drama and Dance
    - Oliver Platt as Pozzo in Waiting for Godot, 1982-03-01; UA070.003.045.00004.00002; Unknown (Box 45)
    - Pozzo (Oliver Platt) holds a rope in Waiting For Godot, 1982-03-01; UA070.003.045.00004.00015 (Box 43)
      Director: Julie Portman. Pozzo, played by Oliver Platt, standing and holding a rope in a university production of Waiting For Godot.
      Plays; Actors; Students; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Department of Drama and Dance; Beckett, Samuel, 1906-1989
    - Pozzo (Oliver Platt) holds a rope as Lucky dances in Waiting For Godot, 1982-03-01; UA070.003.045.00004.00017 (Box 43)
      Director: Julie Portman. Pozzo, played by Oliver Platt, sitting and holding a rope as Lucky dances in a university production of Waiting For Godot.
  - Dead Souls, 1982; UA070.003.045.00005 (Box 45)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 55A; Original description: Major
    - Scene from Dead Souls, 1982-05-01; UA070.003.045.00005.00021 (Box 45)
      Theater; Plays; Drama; Students; Dance--Social aspects; Costumes; photographic print
  - Dead Souls, 1982; UA070.003.045.00006 (Box 45)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 55B; Original description: Major
  - Puntilla and his Hired Man, 1982; UA070.003.045.00007 (Box 45)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 56A; Original description: Major
    - Scene from Puntilla and his Hired Man, 1982-10-01; UA070.003.045.00007.00017 (Box 45)
      Theater; Plays; Drama; Students; Shaving; photographic print; Brecht, Bertolt, 1898-1956
  - Puntilla and his Hired Man, 1982; UA070.003.045.00008 (Box 45)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box 56B; Original description: Major
  - Woyzeck, 1982; UA070.003.045.00009 (Box 45)
    Director: Jacques Chwat. Original box #: Box 57A; Original description: Major
  - Woyzeck, 1982; UA070.003.045.00010 (Box 45)
    Director: Jacques Chwat. Original box #: Box 57B; Original description: Major
  - Ring Round the Moon, 1983; UA070.003.045.00011 (Box 45)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 58A; Original description: Major
    - Scene from Ring Round the Moon, 1983-03-01; UA070.003.045.00011.00001 (Box 45)
      Theater; Plays; Drama; Students; Costumes; photographic print; Fry, Christopher, 1907-2005
  - Ring Round the Moon, 1983; UA070.003.045.00012 (Box 45)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 58B; Original description: Major
  - The Merchant of Venice by Shakespeare, 1983; UA070.003.045.00013 (Box 45)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 59B; Original description: Major
    - A group looks at Shylock (Oliver Platt) in The Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00013.00012 (Box 43)
      Director: Laurence Senelick. Shylock, wearing a white apron and played by Oliver Platt, leads a conversation as others look on in a university production of The Merchant of Venice.
      Plays; Actors; Students; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Department of Drama and Dance; Shakespeare, William
    - Scene from The Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00013.00013 (Box 45)
      Theater; Plays; Drama; Students; Costumes; photographic print; Shakespeare, William
    - Oliver Platt, as Shylock, leading a scene in The Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00013.00016 (Box 43)
      Director: Laurence Senelick. Shylock, wearing a white apron and played by Oliver Platt, leads the scene in a university production of The Merchant of Venice.
  - The Merchant of Venice by Shakespeare, 1983; UA070.003.045.00014 (Box 45)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 59A; Original description: Major
    - Shylock (played by Oliver Platt) and two other characters in the Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00014.00001; Unknown (Box 45)
      Director: Laurence Senelick.
      Actors; Plays; Students; slide (photograph); Platt, Oliver; Shakespeare, William; Dept. of Drama and Dance
    - Scene from the Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00014.00002; Unknown (Box 45)
    - Oliver Platt as Shylock in the Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00014.00003; Unknown (Box 45)
    - Shylock (Oliver Platt) points to his neck in The Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00014.00004 (Box 43)
      Director: Laurence Senelick. Shylock, standing center, wearing a white apron and played by Oliver Platt, points to his neck in a university production of The Merchant of Venice.
    - Shylock (Oliver Platt) confers in the Merchant of Venice, 1983-05-01; UA070.003.045.00014.00005; Unknown (Box 45)
      Director: Laurence Senelick. Shylock, sitting right, wearing a black suit and played by Oliver Platt, confers with a male cast member in a scene from a university production of The Merchant of Venice.
  - The Gingerbread Lady, 1983; UA070.003.045.00015 (Box 45)
    Director: Patricia H. Sankus. Original box #: Box 60; Original description: Summer
  - Deathtrap, 1983; UA070.003.045.00016 (Box 45)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 61; Original description: Summer
  - Born Yesterday, 1983; UA070.003.045.00017 (Box 45)
    Director: Downing Cless Original box #: Box 62; Original description: Summer
  - The Fantasticks, 1983; UA070.003.045.00018 (Box 45)
    Director: Mare Riske. Original box #: Box 63; Original description: Summer
  - Androcles and the Lion, 1983; UA070.003.045.00019 (Box 45)